So guys, welcome to another new
video of mine in which I'm going to tell you about the
chart analysis of ICICI General Insurance.
If you
want to see similar videos and analysis of other stocks, you
can subscribe to my channel,
like the video, and share it
with your friends so they can
make a profit. So, let's analyze this
stock. Look, it has taken a good support
here. If I draw a trend
line for it, it will look something like this.
I draw my trend line.
In this, I
drew a trend line from here. It touched it three times. The
first time it took support, then the
second time it took support again. So, we
could have made a buy here. The third
time it took support, this trend line became
stronger. Now,
if we had made a buy on this third time, we would have made a
huge profit. This chart
analysis tells you this. Okay, and the
black line that I have drawn above was rejecting it repeatedly, it also
broke it well. After that,
I show you the entire chart, this weekly.
Our chart is running; it
took support at this point. After that,
after taking this support,
after such a big consolidation,
it has made a continuous up move. So you can see
how brilliantly it has taken support on its chart. In the
same way, when we analyze a stock, we
see
where it is taking support and what
support it is taking. This is a weekly time frame
chart.
If we go and look at its daily chart,
we will see that the trend line which we
drew a little is very long. There has been a
lot of consolidation in it and the stock
price has also made very good
support on it. Only after the support,
it made a long up move and rally. This means that we do
not have to wait much.
If we keep an eye on the stock for some time and it
takes support on the trend line, then we can make a
buying position in it. If we take
support here on this trend line, then
we have to make a buying position in it.
What happens in this swing trading? We have to
wait with patience.
When we wait with patience.  Only then it gives good results, you
can see how good the up move was,
we have just waited, execution happens
only at 10, otherwise we have to
wait till 90, I do analysis on weekly time frame
because there is
good analysis point to point, candle to candle,
absolutely accurate
analysis on our long time frame
and we get to know clearly where it is taking support and where it is
not taking it
and after that whenever we
make a buying decision, we do it on daily chart
or 15 minute chart, I will meet you
in the next video, till then thank you